PENNY (on TV):
Doctor, please help me.
(Penny(on television):)I think I might be turning
into a killer gorilla.
DOCTOR:
Why do you think you're turning
into a killer gorilla
(Doctor:)and not just a regular gorilla?
PENNY:
Because regular gorillas
are vegetarians,
(Penny(on television):)and I just bit the fingers
off your receptionist!
(Penny screeching like an ape;
chaotic clattering)
(Penny:)Okay, we've seen
plenty.
No!
(Bernadette:)Give me the remote.
(Amy:)Careful. She'll bite
your fingers off.
(Penny:)Okay, well, I've been
poking around the internet,
(Penny:)and I think I found something
we'll enjoy watching even more.
(Amy:)What is it?
(Penny:)Oh, just a video
(Penny:)of Bernadette
in a beauty pageant.
What?!
(Bernadette:)Okay, I learned my lesson.
Making fun of people is wrong!
(Amy:)I haven't learned
my lesson.
Play it! Play it!
(applause)
(Bernadette(on screen):)Hi. I'm Bernadette Maryann
Rostenkowski
(Bernadette(on screen):)from Yorba Linda, California.
(laughing): You look like
a talking cupcake!